Renz Aerol Ravela

A junior information technology student with a passion for the development of technology that helps the community ease their lives. A hard worker and quick learner, I have experience in project development and various collaborations and am always excited to learn more.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CLSU Aquaculture, Science City of Munoz, Nueva Ecija — Student Developer / Designer

FEBRUARY 2023 - PRESENT

- Designed & Developed Android and iOS application for CLSU Aquaculture
- Assist to lessen work by automating the counting of fish fingerlings sold in nearby towns

Central Luzon State University (CLIRDEC Faculty), Science City of Munoz, Nueva Ecija — Student *Developer / Designer*

OCTOBER 2022 - DECEMBER 2023

- Assist the development of web based system for CLSU CLIRDEC Faculty
- Assist to design interactive and user-friendly UI

City College of Technology and Trade Inc., Gapan City, Nueva Ecija — *Student / Trainee*

MAY 2022 - JULY 2022

- Learned various computer system maintenance and basic system administration
- · Assisted other trainee in basic computer assembly and disassembly

EDUCATION

Central Luzon State University, Science City of Munoz, Nueva Ecija — Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (In Progress)

2020 - Present

PROJECTS

FACT: FISH AUTOMATED COUNTING TOOL (Android & iOS) — CLSU Aquaculture, February 2023 – Present (Ongoing)

- An Android and iOS application that helps CLSU Aquaculture in its fingerlings business.
- Help to eliminate manual counting of fingerlings that may take a long time to finish.

Web-Based Classroom Management System — *CLSU CLIRDEC Faculty*, *October* 2022 - *December* 2022

- Developed a system that helps teachers to manage typical classroom information such as student personal information, attendance and grades.
- Improved record accuracy and reduced entry time of data, and an efficient student attendance system that can be used in over 100 classrooms.

P. Silvino Street, Sto Cristo Sur Gapan City, N.E. 3105 (+63) 927-413-7512 renzaerol.ravela@gmail.com in/renz-aerol-ravela renzravela.github.io

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Web and Application
 Development Knowledge in using various technology tools such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Swift, Python, Java, Android Studio.
- Communication Skilled in project collaboration and team involvement.
- Creative Thinking Skilled in using various designing tools such as Figma, Adobe XD and Adobe Photoshop.
- Problem Solving Have experienced solving real-life problems using different technology.

CERTIFICATIONS

Responsive Web Design freecodecamp.org

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freecodecamp.org

The Complete JavaScript Course udemy.org

Web Developer Bootcamp udemy.org

LANGUAGES

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Swift, Python, Java,

Renz Aerol B. Ravela

555, P. Silvino Street, Gapan City, NE 3105 (+63) 927-413-7512 renzaerol.ravela@gmail.com in/renz-aerol-ravela renzravela.github.io

3rd March 2023

Dear Ma'am/Sir,

My name is Renz Aerol Ravela, and I am thrilled to express my interest in the tech job position at your company. I was excited to learn about this position from the website Destination Canada Job Forum. I believe my strong motivation for web and application development and communication/collaboration skills will help me excel as an employee at your company.

As a current information technology student at Central Luzon State University, I gained strong hands and experience in web development. As a developer for our college project, I developed a user-friendly system that can help many users ease their life. I can apply these same skills to create thoughtful and engaging marketing material for your clients.

My dedication for developing, collaborating and finishing projects within tight deadlines make me the perfect candidate for you and your company. And I would like to expand my skills more as a developer and designer through your company.

I'm very excited to learn more about your company and to develop my skills further. Thank you very much for your time and attention. Please reach out to me when you are available to arrange an interview. I look forward to hearing from you soon.

Sincerely,

Renz Aerol B. Ravela